Hi, I'm Johanna Krynytzky and this is Karen Sun Ray and we're here with Hip Expressions Belly Dance Studio in St. Petersburg, Florida.
Let's work on our Rocking Camel.
Now remember a camel is different from an undulation because the shoulders move with the camel, an undulation stays with a confine of the body without having the shoulders move.
So if we put one shoulder in front of the other, so right now I have my left foot in front of my right and not very far forward, so we're not way out here.
Okay.
Feet together, so my toes line up almost with my heel, I want to bend my knees, keep the belly button pulled in.
As I bring the chest forward, I'm going to let the shoulders come forward with me and then lift the chest, bring it back and roll down.
So it's going to be one and two on the front foot and three and four on the back foot.
One and two, back on three and four.
Good.
One, two, three, four.
Now how big you want to make your camel is up to you.
Right?
You can make it nice and big, one, two, three, four.
Or you can refine your camel and make it a little bit smaller, three, four.
One, two, three, let's speed it up a little bit, four.
And; one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, very nice.
Good.
Excellent.
That's a beautiful Rocking Camel.